Call your boss and say I've been a bad
employee.  Punish me.
Mom's boss is my father Loy.
[song voice]
[laughter] It'll be
fun.
Do it, you will enjoy it.   You will enjoy it.   Oh, it will be
fun.   Have you
forgotten your father's number?
[laughter]
Hello.
Hi.
Yes son.
I have been a very bad employee.  You Know.
You should punish me.  Who is saying this?  [Laughs]
Arzoo also told me something, so
according to
Arzoo, how do you know that you work, do you know
or does she know?
[laughs] It's okay, just
punish me.
Hey, I don't force you.
Talk to him.
Hello, yes
son,
yes Papa ji, Namaste
Namaste, someone said that he is a bad employee,
first of all he is not an employee, no no
Papa ji, there was nothing like that, I am
saying that Akanksha is saying,
no no Papa ji, I am not saying that,
we are just telling each other
in which areas we should work.  He was saying
that I don't know that I will call Papa ji and
tell him about the punishment.
Why?
I am not able to understand why are you
saying this?  Is there any
new development?  [laughter]
Hey,
I don't see any new development that would require punishment.
[laughter]
How long will you be coming?
Yes, I am coming in a while, if there is some good
news then bring it.
[Cheering voice]
Amazing brother, amazing friend.  God bless you
both General.  You are amazing general as a couple, man.
[Appreciation]